# RambodRahmani

Artificial Intelligence Engineer

#### **Contact**

Via Pietro Casu, 16 Sassari, (SS) 07100 Italy

(+39) 333 3840979 (+39) 079 2859049

#### Languages

Persian (Mother tongue) Italian (Mother tongue) English (C1) French (A2)



Iran, Italy, Germany, Spain, France, Belgium, Holland, Russia, Hungary.

#### Programming •

C, C++, Java, Python, R, OpenCV, OpenCL, OpenGL, Nvidia CUDA, Julia, ROS, Shell Script.

#### **Software**

Vim, CLion, Matlab, Visual Studio, Eclipse, OMNeT++, VirtualBox, MongoDB, CassandraDB, Git, R Studio, Jupyter Notebook.

#### **Hardware**

Arduino, Raspberry Pi, Embedded Pi, Cubieboard, NVIDIA Jetson.

# Operating Systems $\triangle$

Windows 10, Mac OS X, iOS, Android, Linux Debian, Arch Linux, Raspbian, OpenWRT.

# **Summary**

I was born in Iran in 1993 and moved to Italy at the age of 7. I started studying programming languages at the age of 15 and began to work as a freelance programmer a couple of years later. At the age of 19 I was admitted to the University of Pisa as a Computer Engineering student. After finishing my bachelor I enrolled for a Master in Artificial Intelligence and Data Engineering. In the past years, beside studying for my examinations, I worked for IT Companies, I took part in group projects and tried to startup my own ideas. During the academic year 2017/2018, my goals have shifted. I have developed a deep interest in Artificial Intelligence.

#### **Education**

2020 M.Eng in Artificial Intelligence - 110L/110L (estimated) University of Pisa, Italy
2013 - 2019 B.Eng in Computer Engineering - 98/110L University of Pisa, Italy
2008 - 2013 High School Diploma Scientific Lyceum - 100/100 Scientific Lyceum "G. Spano", Italy

# **University Projects**

2020 **E-Team Squadra Corse** University of Pisa

Autonomous Vehicle Development

My work focused on the development of the driverless autonomous vehicle.

2019 Roborace University of Pisa - E. Piaggio Research Center

Autonomous Vehicle Development

My work focused on the driverless electric vehicle DevBot 2.0.

2015 **PHOS Project** University of Pisa

Software Programmer

Aerospace project at University of Pisa part of the REXUS/BEXUS programme.

## **Papers**

2022 KerubLess - Design of a Driverless Formula SAE Vehicle

2022 IEEE 5th International Conference on Industrial Cyber-Physical Systems

# **Work Experience**

2022 Blue Financial Services IT Firenze

M.Eng Thesis Stage

Development of a machine learning approach for credit score analysis.

2020 R.H. Impianti di Rahmani Hamidreza Consorzio di Bonifica della Nurra

Siemens TIA Portal V16 Developer

Design, development and deployment of a remote monitoring infastructure based on Siemens PLC S7-1200, Simatic HMI TP1200, SINAMICS G120X.

2018 ClassX S.r.I. Pontedera

Java Developer

I worked as Java developer for the ClassX S.r.I focusing to develop broadcasting

software and hardware.

2018 ClassX S.r.I. Pontedera

Intership

Curricular internship Computer Engineering student at University of Pisa.

# 3D Printing

Geeetech Prusa i3

Anycubic I3 Mega

• Creality Ender 3 Pro

Anycubic Photon

# OpenWRT 🛜

As a member of a local hacklab in Pisa, I was involved in installing and configuring the OpenWRT Distribution on embedded devices that we used to build the local Wireless Mesh Network EigenNet.

## Bitcoin B

I have been involved in Bitcoins as far as it. regards Bitcoin Mining, Mining Pools, Bitcoin Wallet and Full Bitcoin Node Configuration (Bitcoin Core).

#### Linkedin in

For full and detailed information regarding my work experience, projects and awards please refer to my Linkedin Profile: it.linkedin.com/in/ rambodrahmani.

## GitHub (7)

"Sharing isn't immoral it's a moral imperative. Only those blinded by greed would refuse to let a friend make a сору."

GitHub Profile:

github.com/ rambodrahmani.

#### 2012 **MALIBU Village**

Internship

I worked as IT Support at MALIBU Village as part of the "Leonardo Project" internship. I had a hands-on experience with Ubiquiti Picostations.

2010 - 2012 **Italian Navv**  San Giorgio-class amphibious transport dock, Italy

Canet-Plage, Languedoc-Roussillon, France

Software Programmer

I coded a set of three software named A.S.C (Acceptance, Sorting and Control) for

the Italian Navy.

2014 - 2015 Boccaccio Club

Pisa, Italy

Software Programmer

Boccaccio Club iOS and Android App Development.

# **Awards, Scholarships and Certificates**

2013 - 2016 **DSU Scholarship** 

DSU of Tuscany

DSU Scholarship by DSU of Tuscany supporting my Bachelor of Engineering

Studies.

2013 - 2016 Italian Ministry of Education, University and Research Scholarship MIUR

Excellence Scholarship by MIUR supporting my Bachelor of Engineering

Studies.

2012 **Intel Excellence in Computer Science**  Intel Corporation

Awarded to Rambod Rahmani for developing the A.S.C. Software.

2012 **National Excellence Registry** 

Italian Ministry of Education, University and Research

Awarded to Rambod Rahmani for developing the A.S.C. Software.

2012 **Certificate of Merit**  Scientific Lyceum "G. Spano", Italy

Awarded to Rambod Rahmani for developing the A.S.C. Software.

**Europass Mobility Nr. IT/00/2012/859/10** 2012

Gymnasium Lyceum "D. A. Azuni" and ALFMED (Académie de Langues France

Méditerranée.).

2011 A.S.C. Software Italian Navy - San Giorgio-class Amphibious Transport Dock

Software Development Certificate by the Italian Navy for developing the A.S.C.

Software.

#### **Events**

May 2015 **International World Wide Web Conference 2015** 

Florence, Italy

Research, development, and applications of the topics related to the Web.

May 2015 **HEUREKA 2015**  Berlin, Germany

One of the main founders conferences in the German-speaking world.

May 2015 **Berlin Talent Summit 2015**  Berlin, Germany

Europe's leading recruiting conference for high-potentials.

July 2012

9th EXPO-SCIENCES EUROPE 2012 (ESE)

Tula, Russia 9th MILSET Expo-Sciences Europe (ESE 2012) held in Tula, Russia.

Federation of Scientific and Technical Associations

I Giovani E Le Scienze 2012 April 2012

The A.S.C. Software was selected as one of the best 30 in the whole country.

#### nterests

Professional: Computational Complexity, Artificial Intelligence, Artificial Neural Networks, Deep Learning, Symbolic Computation, Statistics, Hardware Accelerators, Cloud Computing, Software design, Linux. Personal: Running, Chess, Cosmology, Astronomical observations, Stock Market, Quantitative trading,

Last updated: January 24,

2023